tocom.or.jp 2005-03-08

# TOCOM Privacy Statement

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

> Personal information gathered by this website is used to contact users for such purposes as sending information or responding to queries.  When collecting personal information, it is always done by lawful and fair means.
> 
> If TOCOM believes that any of the following cases apply, TOCOM may use or provide personal information for a purpose other than the original purpose of collection, with the greatest possible consideration of the rights and interests of the person involved.
> 
> 1.
> 
> | 
> 
> If the information must be used or provided in order to comply with laws or regulations;  
>   
> ---|---  
>   
> 2.
> 
> | 
> 
> If the personal information is to be used internally by TOCOM, only to the extent necessary for TOCOM to conduct its business, and only if there is a legitimate reason for its use.  
>   
> Among the information gathered by TOCOM through any means such as this website, fax, telephone, letters, etc., personal information refers to the name, address, E-mail address, telephone number, occupation, and other information that identifies specific individuals. TOCOM only collects data that is needed to conduct its business, and no information, such as credit card numbers and bank account details, will be gathered which has no direct relation to its business.

### Management of Personal Information

> TOCOM takes all necessary measures for the appropriate management of personal information to prevent its disclosure, loss or destruction. TOCOM limits the number of authorized persons with access to databases containing personal information, so as to ensure that there is no improper access from outside the Exchange, as well as no improper usage within the Exchange.
> 
> In principle, TOCOM determines a retention period for the personal information that it manages, which is considered to be within the range of time necessary for the purpose of its use. When this retention period has lapsed, or when the purpose of its use has been accomplished, the personal information shall be immediately deleted unless the following cases apply:

> 1\. 
> 
> | 
> 
> The personal information must be retained to comply with laws or regulations;  
>   
> ---|---  
> 2. | There is a legitimate reason for not deleting personal information that is being retained only to the extent necessary for TOCOM to conduct its business.  
>   
> If TOCOM entrusts the handling of personal information to a party outside the Exchange, TOCOM shall select a party that is recognized to be capable of handling it properly.  Contracts for such work shall stipulate rules that ensure the proper maintenance and management of personal information. These shall include necessary measures, confidentiality, and the prohibition of redistributing such data.

### Disclosure and Amendment of Information

> If a user requests the disclosure of his or her personal information, TOCOM shall disclose all relevant personal information without delay. However, if TOCOM believes that any of the following cases apply, TOCOM may not disclose all or part of the personal information relevant to the request.

> 1. | If doing so will significantly interfere with the conduct of TOCOM’s business;   
> ---|---  
> 2. | If there is a risk that disclosure will harm the life, body, assets or other interests of the individual.   
>   
> If a user requests the amendment, addition or deletion of his or her personal information, TOCOM shall investigate the situation without delay. If TOCOM recognizes that there is an error in the personal information relevant to the request, if the retention period has lapsed, or if there are any other reasons requiring amendment, addition or deletion, then TOCOM shall amend or otherwise modify the information without delay.
